thekrazycouponlady.com 2016-12-29

# The Krazy Coupon Lady Privacy Policy - The Krazy Coupon Lady

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or zip code. This is known as a form of Personally Identifiable Information (PII) and represents information that can be used to identify or locate a single person. We protect all data but most notably PII.

You may, if you choose, visit our site anonymously.

If you choose to use our mobile “app”, data about what you visit in our app and how long you stay there is made available to us. We may or may not use that information but when we do, it is solely to improve the experience of all mobile users within the app.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Information Security. We use secure computing practices to safeguard personal information we collect to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure.

Employee Access, Training and Expectations. Our ethical standards and employee policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables sites or service provider's systems to recognize your browser, and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools to you in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf, except to help us conduct and improve our business.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your internet browsing history. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TChMxcc5beDZXXi1AUmcT7HMsfRuXbvS0TkOoYRaC51pV-WpiKTOhl30xoOIOXWVkAIo6817Jlrz1vjJKc30z2kP7VWrTnrjJ77vvtHunTn_UONJHw5JTTdBLfPd0uk4keLxhUG5SB4PnaVp2DaqMjh4tp3wzqS-vf6YnII-FVxxPg_N7io) at Google. You may opt out of advertising from any or all Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) members at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell or trade your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) without providing you advance notice. We may share your PII data with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other's rights, property, or safety. Non-PII visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. In some cases, we may share hashed or obfuscated email addresses to better augment what data is shown to you based on geographical information and other preference patterns. Your email address or any other PII is never shared in its raw form.

**Third party links**

At our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

We also may be compensated in exchange for featured placement of certain sponsored products and services, or your clicking on certain links posted on this website.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act (OPPA). We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As parties protected by the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the ‘Profile' page.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the email address below:
